Wilbert F. Rodrigo

Over my 9 years of teaching experience and 2 years of managerial in the Quick Service Restaurant industry, I garnered confidence and expertise in dealing with people professionally. Carefully work hand on hand with the needs of learners by adapting factors affecting their learning. Carefully following process of customer handling scenario specifically in time of complaints and inquiries.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teacher / Disaster Risk Reduction and Management Coordinator

Antipolo National High School

May 2013 – Present

Tasks

- Setting and enforcing standards for student behavior in the classroom.
- Preparing courses, modules, and projects to fulfill learning goals.
- Adapting teaching methods and materials to meet the interests and learning styles of students
- Daily creating lessons logs and audio-visual presentations
- Conduct trainings/seminars and drills to increase disaster resiliency of the students, teaching, and non-teaching personnel.
- Perform basic first aid to the students/personnel who acquired injuries.
- Prepare and disseminate contingency plan of the school

Store Manager

Jollibee Foods Corporation May 2011 – April 2013

Tasks

- In charge of hiring, training, and supervising workers in the food service industry.
- Scheduling employee hours to guarantee that every shift is properly covered.
- Completing payroll and keeping track of employee information.
- Ensuring that clients receive timely, high-quality meal service.
- Ensuring that all work locations are regularly inspected for conformity with food safety and health laws.
- Taking stock of the food and other consumables, placing orders for what is required, and receiving deliveries.
- Tallying all cash and charge slips accurately.
- Reviewing sales data to identify the most profitable menu items.
- Arranging for deep cleaning, pest control, garbage collection, and equipment maintenance as necessary.
- After the closing of business, turning off all lights and activating the alarm system.

EDUCATION

Study Program

University of Rizal System

Master in Business Administration

June 2017 – Present

Polytechnic University of the Philippines

May 2007 – May 2011

Bachelor in Business Teacher Education

LICENSED/CERTIFICATES

PRC Licensed Teacher

National Competency III in Bookkeeping

SKILLS

Organized / Attention to detail

Dedicated and determined

Fast Learner

Strong written and verbal communication skills

Strong time-management skills

Problem-solving skills

Multi-tasking skills

Ability to work independently

Technical Skills: MS Office and G Suite/Google Workspace

LANGUAGES

Full Professional working proficiency

INTERESTS

Outdoor Sports

Web Search

Web Design